[{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664857717,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":21298,"timeElapsed":37495},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664868568,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":10848,"timeElapsed":48347},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664882625,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":14052,"timeElapsed":62403},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664895038,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":12409,"timeElapsed":74817},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664902042,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":7000,"timeElapsed":81821},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664911945,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":9900,"timeElapsed":91724},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664915249,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":3301,"timeElapsed":95028},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664932457,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":17204,"timeElapsed":112236},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664942513,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":10053,"timeElapsed":122292},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664958048,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":14286,"timeElapsed":137827},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664967200,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":9150,"timeElapsed":146979},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664974138,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6934,"timeElapsed":153917},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664982841,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":8700,"timeElapsed":162620},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664987633,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4789,"timeElapsed":167411},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664991241,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3606,"timeElapsed":171020},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664993977,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2733,"timeElapsed":173756},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664996896,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2917,"timeElapsed":176675},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665006441,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":9542,"timeElapsed":186219},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665009985,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3542,"timeElapsed":189763},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665021529,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":10425,"timeElapsed":201308},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665024961,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3428,"timeElapsed":204739},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665030401,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":5438,"timeElapsed":210180},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665033472,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3069,"timeElapsed":213251},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665039992,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":6517,"timeElapsed":219771},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665046744,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":6750,"timeElapsed":226523},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665050473,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":3727,"timeElapsed":230252},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665056465,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":5989,"timeElapsed":236244},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665067017,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":10550,"timeElapsed":246796},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665070144,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3122,"timeElapsed":249923},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665078633,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":7547,"timeElapsed":258412},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665081913,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3278,"timeElapsed":261692},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665085866,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3950,"timeElapsed":265644},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665092649,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":6780,"timeElapsed":272428},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665095192,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2541,"timeElapsed":274971},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665097761,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":2566,"timeElapsed":277540},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665099977,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2213,"timeElapsed":279756},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665105970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":5990,"timeElapsed":285748},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665110569,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":4595,"timeElapsed":290348},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665121675,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":10186,"timeElapsed":301454},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665129482,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":7805,"timeElapsed":309261},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665137905,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":8421,"timeElapsed":317684},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665140667,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":2759,"timeElapsed":320446},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665144202,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3531,"timeElapsed":323981},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665146588,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2382,"timeElapsed":326366},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665148633,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2043,"timeElapsed":328412},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665156337,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":7701,"timeElapsed":336116},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665158793,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2454,"timeElapsed":338572},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665166090,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":6234,"timeElapsed":345869},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665169176,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3083,"timeElapsed":348954},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665172937,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":3759,"timeElapsed":352716},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665177538,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":4597,"timeElapsed":357317},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665179937,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2397,"timeElapsed":359716},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665182033,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2093,"timeElapsed":361812},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665185594,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3558,"timeElapsed":365373},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665191722,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":6125,"timeElapsed":371501},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665194122,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2396,"timeElapsed":373901},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665202297,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":7200,"timeElapsed":382076},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665204034,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1735,"timeElapsed":383813},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665207169,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3133,"timeElapsed":386948},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665210313,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3141,"timeElapsed":390092},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665213329,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3013,"timeElapsed":393108},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665216105,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2775,"timeElapsed":395884},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665218640,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2532,"timeElapsed":398419},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665221809,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3167,"timeElapsed":401588},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665224497,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2686,"timeElapsed":404276},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665243570,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":17925,"timeElapsed":423349},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665250634,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":7061,"timeElapsed":430413},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665256338,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":5700,"timeElapsed":436116},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665259689,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":3349,"timeElapsed":439468},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665262345,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2652,"timeElapsed":442124},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665264857,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2510,"timeElapsed":444636},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665267289,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2430,"timeElapsed":447068},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665271154,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":3863,"timeElapsed":450933},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665274345,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3188,"timeElapsed":454124},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665287393,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":11929,"timeElapsed":467172},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665293713,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":6317,"timeElapsed":473492},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665296898,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":3182,"timeElapsed":476676},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665299448,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2548,"timeElapsed":479227},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665302929,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":3478,"timeElapsed":482707},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665305569,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2639,"timeElapsed":485348},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665307649,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2076,"timeElapsed":487428},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665310865,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3213,"timeElapsed":490644},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665316184,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":5316,"timeElapsed":495963},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665324371,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":7046,"timeElapsed":504150},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665330913,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":6539,"timeElapsed":510692},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665334026,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3109,"timeElapsed":513804},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665336953,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2924,"timeElapsed":516732},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665340865,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3909,"timeElapsed":520644},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665343824,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2957,"timeElapsed":523603},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665346681,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2854,"timeElapsed":526460},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665352835,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":6151,"timeElapsed":532614},{"subjectID":"lzwob3pv1m","prolificID":"5b2bcfb51835660001cc6751","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742165a27970e0fcd66a23","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665356265,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3426,"timeElapsed":536044}]